You've got it wrong, Lyle. It is coming Tuesday.
一定是你弄错了   莱尔   是星期二
No! Monday, Lois!
不   是星期一   露易丝
Positively, Tuesday.
肯定是星期二
Absolutely, Monday.
绝对是星期一
Tuesday!
星期二
Monday!
星期一
Stop! What you both are...
停   你们俩个在
I mean... talking about?
我的意思是   你们在讨论些什么
Something very important that's happening this Tuesday, Finley love.
一件很重要的事   就要在星期二到来了 亲爱的芬利
Very important indeed. Except it's Monday.
事实上的确很重要   但是在星期一到来
So, what is it?
到底是什么事
It's the truck yard's ten-year anniversary.
我们卡车围场十周年纪念日
Wow! Eh...What's an anniversary?
哇   呃   什么是纪念日
Wow, it's like a birthday. It's something only comes once a year.
哦   纪念日类似于生日   每年只有一次
And Lyle and I in the truck yard have been here ten years.
我和莱尔在卡车围场已经待了十年啦
Ten whole years? That's older than I am.
十整年吗   这可比我的年龄都大呢
-That's right.  -Yeah.
-对呀  -是的
That's very important. How are you going to celebrate?
这是一件很重要的事   你们打算怎么庆祝呢
We haven't really thought about it now.
实际上我们还没有想过这个
Leave it all to me!
那就全权交给我办吧